foobies.com 2015-12-31

# FARK.com: Frequently Asked Questions: Legal Stuff

> ## Legal Stuff
> 
> ### Fark's Legal and Privacy Statement
> 
> #### Terms Of Service
> 
> Text comments and Photoshopped images posted on Fark by registered users may not be reposted or broadcast without the express written permission or license from Fark.com, and must attribute Fark.com as the source. 
> 
> By using Fark, You agree that you will not use any robot, harvesting bots, spider, scraper, or other automated means to access the site for any purpose without our express written permission. You further agree that You will not take any action that imposes or may impose (in our sole discretion) an unreasonable or disproportionately large load on our infrastructure or interfere or attempt to interfere with the proper working of the site or any activities conducted on the site. 
> 
> #### Copyright Notice
> 
> By posting an image or other content or by making a comment, you represent and warrant to Fark that (1) doing so does not violate or infringe anyone else's rights; and (2) you created the file or other content you are uploading, or otherwise have sufficient intellectual property rights to upload the material consistent with these terms. 
> 
> By posting content, you are confirming that the content is yours and that the uploading and use of your content does not violate the privacy rights, publicity rights, copyrights, contract rights, trademark right, or any other intellectual property rights of any other party. If we learn, or become aware, that you are infringing the rights of others or are using content that is not your own (or have the permission to use same), Fark retains the right to remove this content and you agree that you are responsible for any costs, fees, fines, penalties, judgments and/or legal fees associated with the infringement, regardless of whether the infringement occurred with or without your knowledge (i.e. the responsibility is yours to ensure you are the owner or have rights to post prior to posting) 
> 
> When you make your content public (i.e. by posting or submitting to our website), you grant Fark a worldwide, non-exclusive, royalty-free license (with sublicense and assignment rights) to copy, distribute, stream, post publicly display (e.g. post it elsewhere), reproduce and create derivative works from it (meaning things based on it), anywhere, whether in print or any kind of electronic version that exists now or is later developed, to create derivative works of, to allow downloads of, and/or distribute any such file or content for any purpose, including a commercial purpose. 
> 
> Copyrights and Copyright Agents. We respect the intellectual property of others, and we ask you to do the same. If you believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please provide our Copyright Agent with the following information (see 17 U.S.C. 512 (c)(3) for further detail): 
> 
>   * An electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright interest;
>   * Description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed;
>   * A description of where the material that you claim is infringing is located on Fark.com;
>   * Your address, telephone number, and email address;
>   * A statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and
>   * A statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in your Notice is accurate and that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner's behalf.
> 

> 
> Our Copyright Agent for notice of claims of copyright infringement on Fark.com is Drew Curtis, who can be reached through farkback at: <http://www.fark.com/feedback/legal>
> 
> Fark, TotalFark, Foobies, Fark This, and the Fark, TotalFark, and Foobies logos, are registered trademarks of Fark, Inc. Farked is a trademark of Fark, Inc. 
> 
> Fark respects the intellectual property rights of others and expects its users to do the same. In accordance with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act ("DMCA"), the text of which may be found on the U.S. Copyright Office website at <http://www.copyright.gov/legislation/dmca.pdf>, Fark will respond expeditiously to notices of alleged infringement that are reported to our designated agent, identified in the sample notice below. 
> 
> If you see anything on our site that you believe infringes your copyright rights, you may notify our Digital Millennium Copyright Act ("DMCA") agent by sending the following information: 
> 
> Identification of the copyrighted work or works claimed to have been infringed; Identification of the material on our servers that is claimed to be infringing and that is to be removed, including the URL of the Fark thread in question or other information to enable us to locate the material; A statement that you have a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by you as copyright owner, or by your agent, or by law; A statement that the information in your notice is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that you are the owner (or authorized to act on behalf of the owner) of the exclusive copyright right that is allegedly being infringed. Your physical or electronic signature, or of someone authorized to act on your behalf; Instructions on how we may contact you: preferably email, but also address and phone 
> 
> Our agent to receive such notifications of claimed infringement is Drew Curtis. 
> 
> DMCA/Copyright infringement contact email: dmca@fark.com 
> 
> Fark utilizes the same procedure(s) for any claimed trademark violations or other infringements. If we receive a DMCA notice and remove something you submitted anonymously, we will have no way of notifying you, you will have to contact us if you think that may have occurred. Keep in mind that Fark reserves the right to remove any content, at any time, whether or not it infringes or violates any of our policies. 
> 
> #### Fark logos and trademarks
> 
> Fark welcomes the use of the Fark logo and trademark to promote, reference, or link back to Fark.com or associated accounts. Below are some logos that can be used for this purpose: 
> 
>   
>  Smallest light: 
> 
> Small light: 
> 
> Medium light: 
> 
> Large light: 
> 
> Medium transparent: 
> 
> Smallest dark: 
> 
> Small dark: 
> 
> Medium dark: 
> 
> Large dark: 
> 
> Fark consents to the above logos being slightly cropped or adjusted to fit a differently-sized standard on other sites, as long as the name "Fark" is still clearly legible. For legibility, the logo should be no less than 25 pixels in height. 
> 
> #### Fark's Privacy Policy
> 
> **Short Version**
> 
> We will not give your addresses to third parties. We hate spammers. Bunch of jackasses is what they are. 
> 
> **Longer Official Version**
> 
> Fark is committed to user privacy in our products and services. This policy outlines our personal information handling practices. If you give us personal information, we will treat it according to this policy. 
> 
> Fark encourages you to read this privacy policy and those of all web sites you visit. Below is a summary of Fark's online privacy policy. 
> 
> **Types and uses of personal information**
> 
> Your personal information is used in the following ways: 
> 
>   * User IDs and Passwords. Provides you with access to your profile areas and to protected content.
>   * Account Information. These tell us more about who you are, how to contact you, and your shipping and billing information.
>   * Customer Feedback and Support. Provides a mechanism for requesting information from Fark. Also used to tell us how we can improve our products, services and site designs.
>   * Email Correspondence. Used to raise and respond to issues and inquiries of all types. Also used to distribute information about Fark, our products, and services.
>   * Transactions. Shows which products and services you have requested.
> 

> 
> We will only use your personal information in the ways specified when it was collected. We will not subsequently change the way in which we use your personal information unless you consent to the new usage. 
> 
> **Security measures**
> 
> We protect the personal information you share with us. 
> 
> Authorized third party agents may also need access to some of your personal information. For example, if we need to ship something to you, we must share your name and address with a shipping company. We only provide third party agents with the minimum amount of information needed to complete the requested service or transaction. We do not otherwise share your personal information with third parties unless you have granted us permission to do so. 
> 
> **Data Retention**
> 
> Fark will not retain your personal information longer than is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected. 
> 
> **Linked web sites**
> 
> We provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control these Web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third party sites. 
> 
> **Children's privacy**
> 
> We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems. 
> 
> Fark encourages parents to go online with their kids. Here are a few tips to help make a child's online experience safer: 
> 
>   * Teach kids never to give personal information, unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult. Includes name, address, phone, school, etc
>   * Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate.
>   * Look for Web site privacy policies. Know how your child's information is treated.
> 

> 
> Check out the FTC's site(1) for more tips on protecting children's privacy online. 
> 
> We may display advertisements from third parties. Third party ad-serving companies control which ads are shown. These ad-serving companies may use cookies to collect non-personally identifiable information from you. Advertisers use this information to target the ads and measure their impact. 
> 
> **Third Party Advertising**
> 
> We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. For more information on online behavioral advertising, privacy, cookies, and how this all works, please see the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/learn_more.asp) page on this topic. 
> 
> **Third Party Cookies**
> 
> In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 
> 
> You can opt-out of Google Adsense advertising cookies by going to <http://www.google.com/ads/preferences>. 
> 
> You can opt-out of other third-party advertising cookies by using the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out tool at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 
> 
> **Audience Analytics**
> 
> In order to understand our audience, and understand how our audience interacts with Fark, we use a few different analytics products. Each of these places a cookie on your computer to gather information about the Fark pages you visit, how long you stay on the site, etc. 
> 
> This information is aggregated so we can see general patterns. None of the information you provide on sign-up or while using the site is ever provided. 
> 
> One of these analytics products is Google Analytics. We send the Fark Account Number assigned to you at sign-up time to Google Analytics to understand how our users use Fark across different devices. Google has no way to associate this with any other personally identifiable information inside of Analytics. If you don't want us to send your Fark Account Number to Google Analytics, you can check the box in your [Preferences](http://www.fark.com/users/0/prefs) that says "Don't send my Fark Account Number to Google Analyics". 
> 
> **Policy updates**
> 
> All updates to this policy will be posted here. 
> 
> Note: This policy also covers the personal information you provide to Fark Customer Support.
